Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/võ-huyền-trang-5988511b9 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

React.js

Node.js

Web Applications

Languages

English (Professional Working)

Võ Huyền Trang

Full-stack dev at GEO system solutions Vietnam Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

Experienced Frontend Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Web development and English. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Science in Computer Science focused in Computer Science from VNUHCM-University of Information Technology.

Experience

GEO system solutions Vietnam 4 years 5 months

Full Stack Developer April 2021 - Present (4 years 2 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Frontend Developer
January 2021 - April 2021 (4 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Education

University of Information Technology
Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (September 2016 - November 2020)